Thank you
so
much
for your attention.
Let's go.
Thank you.
Oh, oh, oh, oh
In this news is an explosion
today in the city of Cahira.
I believe that the cause of the
explosion is the gas in the earth.
And I believe that these things
are not any problems on the site?
And we have already been told about the
events that happened in the Shara Al-Ghiza?
In the region of the Hrameath.
Run, Kyotaro!
Keep your distance!
Is that all, Johto?
Is that all the power you've got?
Bastard.
Why don't we see who's the fastest?
Not even remotely close.
So many, so many, the world!
The time has frozen.
This guy is a mystery.
With his inferior level of stand power,
I don't understand why he was
able to survive my attack.
The grand finale was unexpectedly simple
The Joestar bloodline that has pestered me
The all-powerful Dio Has
finally come to an end
What?
I'm banged up alright, but I'm alive.
What the hell?
Why have I survived again?
Jotaro, what did you do just now?
I'm asking you what did you do just now?
Why are you alive?
Don't know, but it looks like your
stand ain't all it's cracked up to be.
Hold your tongue.
The world.
What?
But that is.
Can't be.
Star Platinum.
Without any conscious effort, Star
Platinum has been protecting me all along.
I'd swear that for a second I could
see him move inside the frozen time.
Move.
It's incredible!
Jotaro...
His star platinum and mine, the
world, are similar types of stands.
How very unexpected of Star Platinum
to come into my frozen world.
You watched me from
within the frozen time.
Hmm, not unlike a child learning
how to first ride a bicycle.
He'll get the hang of it in no time.
After Kakyoin revealed
the secret of the world,
you were able to figure out
the idea of time freeze,
and then become aware of
moving inside the frozen time.
I suppose your comrade's death
was not wasted after all.
You killed Kakyoin!
So now,
I have to say to myself,
about how many seconds are you actually
able to move within the frozen time?
one second or two seconds or maybe you
can move around for five seconds or so?
in frozen time like me and are
just pretending that you can't!
this is bad!
he's able to move for five seconds before
it took everything I had to move for!
just an instant I can't let Dio know that
it's not enough time for me to fight!
back well I'm sure you don't want me to
know about it but from what I can see you!
you are able to move around
only for an instant at best,
but you are able to move
inside the! frozen time,
no matter how brief, and to approach
you without caution is not something?
a wise person would do.
The attack you made earlier
was quite stimulating.
Ah, but Jotaro...
Regardless of all that, I just
thought of a way to execute you.
You're quite pale.
Have you realized that your end will
be much more terrible than Joseph's?
A useless gesture!
I have you in checkmate!
The world!
Explain to me how you're going
to get away from these knives.
Joltaro!
The fact that you can see makes
it all the more frightening.
If you don't do something about it now,
you're going to have problems later.
Is that the best you can do?
Now it has been proven that you can
only move for an instant at a time.
And that time is up.
It's all over, but one more to be sure!
To tell you the truth, I'm relieved that
I was finally able to kill you, Jotaro.
You surprised me when you were able
to enter my world of frozen time.
Oh, what a pain.
How dare he put holes in
my prized school jacket.
I managed to survive, thanks to the
splints I put on my broken ribs.
But I've taken some heavy damage.
I've got no choice but to play
dead and wait for my chance.
If he throws knives at me again, I
don't think I'll be able to dodge them.
I gotta deliver a direct blow to his head.
Is he dead?
I don't know.
I can't be too careful when
dealing with the Joestars.
This is the first time that
I, Dio, have felt fear.
I shouldn't go near him carelessly.
He might be playing dead.
How about his breathing?
I can't hear anything.
He's not breathing.
How about...
His heart beat.
This sucks.
Damn, if I pass out now.
Seriously, I'm a dead man.
It's like some kind of bad joke to stop my
heart with my own stand
and to die from it.
And die from it.
His heart is not beating.
He is indeed dead.
Well, just to be extra
careful, I'll sever his head.
To ensure peace of mind.
Right, Jotaro?
This is the end.
Go straight to hell, D .O.
Call the ref.
How are you able to defeat Eist?
What the heck?
At last, at last I was able to
deliver a direct blow to his head.
Got here in time.
Did you finish off Dio?
Polnareff, your injuries.
Forget about my injuries and get him!
Avenge the deaths of Iggy and Avdol.
Iggy.
Bastard.
Dammit.
I can't move anymore.
Don't try to talk, Polnareff.
This is really pathetic.
Just wait here.
I've got something to do.
I'm going to kill you.
What's happened to me?
My legs are weak.
My head is splitting and I feel nauseous.
How can this be happening?
That I deal, feel sick.
I, Dio, can't stand up because
Jotaro damaged my head.
Dio, you're not getting away with this.
Time to give up.
Hahaha!
The world!
Now time?
Will flow.
Got to make it!
If I can just make it to that place?
I almost made it.
If I can just get there, to that place!
No more of this playing tag.
You gotta give up now, Dio.
Time freezes.
The world...
I got you, Jotaro.
You may not realize it yet, but you
just lost to Dio in this game of wits.
Does this street look familiar to you?
or being the tourist that you
are, do all streets look the same?
This street, can it be?
That's right.
This is the escape route that allowed
me to suck the blood of Joseph Joestar.
Why, you?
It's fitting.
It's fitting well.
Feels good.
This body belongs to my age-old
enemy, Jonathan Joestar.
The blood I sucked is
his grandson Joseph's,
and it is his grandson who
allowed me to escape, Jotaro.
The bloodline of Joestar
has been a nuisance to me,
not unlike a piece of dog shit in
the middle of the road to my destiny.
But in the very end, you are all
meant to be useful to me, Dio.
I'll stop you.
You don't really know
what you're talking about.
Watch this!
He's squeezed bone dry like you will be.
No one could remain
unaffected after seeing that.
Dio, you've done it.
You've pissed me off.
Then this is the final round. Let's go.
The world!
Time is frozen!
Quite impressive, Jotaro.
You're actually prolonging
the time you can move around.
But I'm beginning to feel more power.
Thanks to my new supply of Joestar blood!
I am exploding with stand power!
Stick straight to the bottom, Jotaro!
Not yet.
It's not enough.
I'm not angry enough yet!
Everybody stay clear of him! Make way!
Hmph.
Hmm...
Aaaaah!
Nooo!
It feels great!
This incredible surge of power!
Nooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo
Let's dispense with the
warm-up, shall we, Jotaro?
This is the last time I freeze time.
The world!
I'm worried that he's not showing himself.
But it doesn't matter.
I've decided what I'm going to do.
I'll blast Star Platinum against
him for as long as I can move.
There's one thing I'm very sure of, Dio.
The next time I see your face,
I'm probably gonna lose it.
I will go totally berserk.
Come on, Dio.
An oil tanker for you!
Crushed to death!
It's over.
At last, I've stamped out
the bloodline of Joestar.
Now it is proven that no one is
greater in the world than I, Dio.
You insignificant human beings.
I shall rule over you.
You will grovel at my feet.
Ha ha ha!
Ha
ha
ha!
What?
I.. I can't move.
It can't be!
My body isn't moving at all!
Looks like you've moved all you can.
Wha...
What the...
I'm the one who froze time.
Jotaro...
How does it feel?
What's it like wanting
so desperately to move?
And now time flows.
There's no mercy in my heart for you.
I don't feel sorry for you one bit.
Unfortunately I still have a conscience.
So torturing you to death would
probably leave a bad taste in my mouth.
How many seconds will it
take for that leg to heal?
I'm gonna blast you with my star
platinum just as soon as you recover.
So bring it on.
How dare you insult me.
But Jotaro, even now, at this crucial
moment, you are, after all, only human.
And your way of thinking
is extremely limited.
Does that leave a bad taste in your mouth?
Such thinking is equivalent to rat shit in
a pit, and it will be your fatal mistake.
I, Dio, am different.
There is only one simple ideal.
Victory and conquest, that's all.
The process and method
doesn't really matter!
Gotcha!
Die!
Get! I
can't!
Dio!
Dio cannot die!
There's only one reason
for your defeat, Dio.
One simple little thing and that's
all you really really pissed me off.
And then when I woke up I was in the Speed
Wagon Foundation's paramedic helicopter.
Through my comrades'
battle, and a blood transfusion from Dio's
remains, yes, I was able to be revived.
I owe it all to my grandson, and to the
precious lives that can never be restored.
The terrifying evil is now
disappearing into the Red Sea,
along with the shimmer of the morning sun.
As long as I live, I will never
forget about this journey, this site.
And Kakyoin,
Iggy, Avdol,
it's over.
Why do you insist on going
back to France, Polnareff?
You don't have any family there, right?
So why not come to my place?
Come to New York.
Mr.
Joestar, although I have no family
left, France is my homeland.
I think often of my hometown.
No matter where I go, it is
the place I always return to.
Don't hesitate to call me.
I'll come as fast as I can.
From anywhere in the world
I might happen to be.
Well, I'll certainly miss you.
We had many painful and
difficult situations.
But I wouldn't have
missed it for the world.
Because of all of you,
the journey was enjoyable.
Yes, that's true.
I enjoyed it as well, from
the bottom of my heart.
I'll see you later.
Try not to get yourself killed!
You hear, old man?
You and your damn grandson
Don't you two forget about me, okay?
We'll see you again.
Unless you try to steer
clear of me, that is!
Right then.
Farewell.
Nobody could ever forget a guy like you!
Even if they really wanted to.
Take care now.
Mama, Mama, wake up!
Holly!
Why, why, you're...
You're awake!
Are you feeling alright?
Yes.
All of a sudden, I just
feel completely fine again.
In any case, we have to get ready. Huh?
They'll be coming home soon.
Papa and Jotaro.
I know it, Mama. Very soon.
They'll be coming home at last.
Thank you.